<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rebel Tools</title>
    <description>We are a bunch of free multi-disciplinary individuals comprising of software and hardware engineers, designers and mobile specialists. Each of us with years of experience working in this line, you can be assured you will always be covered by the best.</description>
    <link>http://rebel.tools/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 19:18:56 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 19:18:56 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Project 1</title>
        <description>Setting up Jibber is a breeze! The first step is to drag and drop the framework into your Xcode project. Then, head on over to your Project Settings, and under the General tab, scroll down to Linked Frameworks and Libraries, and add libz.dylib. Finally, add -ObjC to your Other Linker Flags, that can be found under Build Settings. You can skip this step if you&#39;re using Cocoapods, as this would have already been set. And that&#39;s it! Your project is all set up to use Jibber!</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://rebel.tools/web%20development/2014/07/15/project-1/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://rebel.tools/web%20development/2014/07/15/project-1/</guid>
        
        
        <category>web development</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Project 2</title>
        <description>Jibber lists all the network requests that you make via your phone or simulator. The URL that you are using will be displayed at the top. The requests parameters that you send will be displayed in the top half of the app, and the response will be displayed in the bottom half. The history of network requests that you have made will be displayed in the sidebar.</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://rebel.tools/web%20development/2014/07/14/project-2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://rebel.tools/web%20development/2014/07/14/project-2/</guid>
        
        
        <category>web development</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Project 3</title>
        <description>Easily browse through your previous network requests and seamlessly debug your data! Jibber is simple to use, and will save you tons of time when dealing with apps using network requests!</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://rebel.tools/web%20development/2014/03/14/project-3/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://rebel.tools/web%20development/2014/03/14/project-3/</guid>
        
        
        <category>web development</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
